Guide to the Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill 1974-1981 (Bulk 1975-1979) RG.3.0.8
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administration
  - Academic Matters; Program Development; Announcements and Circular Memos, Presidents, Jul 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Academic Matters; Program Development; Announcements and Circular Memos, Presidents, May 1976-Dec 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Academic Matters; Program Development; Announcements and Circular Memos, Presidents, Feb 1978-Aug 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Academic Matters; Program Development; Announcements and Circular Memos, Presidents, Sep 1979-Jun 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Archives, Jun 1974-Sep 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Art Collection, Apr 1975-Nov 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Art Collection, May 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Art Collection, Oct 1977-Jun 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bicentennial of U.S. at NYU, Sep 1975-Jan 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Computers, Jul 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Computers, Jun 1976-Sep 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Consultants, May 1975-Jan 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Legal Correspondence, Dec 1975-Aug 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Legal Opinions (NYU), Jul 1975-Mar 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Libraries, Oct 1974-Aug 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Libraries, Sep 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Libraries, Mar 1976-May 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Libraries, Jun 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Libraries, Sep 1976-May 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Libraries, Jun 1977-Mar 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Libraries, Jun 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Libraries, Jan 1979-Aug 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Libraries; Acquisitions, May 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Libraries; Libraries/Bookstore Taskforce, Oct 1975-May 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Libraries; Working Plans on Structure, Functions, and Operations of Bobst, Mar 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Libraries; Office Services, Nov 1975-Jul 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Libraries; Office Services, Jan 1977-Jul 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Reorganization, May 1975-Jun 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Reorganization, Nov 1976-Jan 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Research and Planning, May 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Research and Planning, Oct 1976-Aug 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Research and Planning, Sep 1978-Apr 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Work and Development Plans, Sep 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Series II: Associations
  Scope and Contents note
  Series II is comprised of 8 boxes totaling 3.33 linear feet. Its content stems from John Crittenden Sawhill's extramural worklife while at NYU, both NYU and non-NYU-related, and more than substantiates his "workaholic" persona; for this self-definition, see Sawhill to Maurice Greenberg 7/11/78, Box 14, folder 7. The broad variety of activity represented in this series has been divided into four subseries, defined as follows: subseries I, NYU-Related, New York City, etc.; subseries II, not-for-profit, energy, etc.; subseries III, directorships; subseries IV, higher education, corporate, personal, etc.
  Subseries I, Box 8 contains rather a mix of information. Some Committee for Astor Place items are found in folder 17; additional material titled Astor Place Improvement is located in Box 40, folders 10-12. Box 9, folders 1-3 offers an immediate impression of Sawhill's range of initiatives during his presidency; in folder I, approaches to the corporate community; folder 2, a talk on the case for the liberal arts; folder 3, his role on New York City's Emergency Financial Control Board.
  Subseries II offers substance to the picture of Sawhill's on-going involvement in national energy policy review and advocacy, see the Aspen Institute sequence, Box 10, folders 16-19, Box 11, folders 1-5, and Box 12, folder 5, Shimoda (Japan) Conference, Box 12, folders 15-17, and Mitre Corporation, Box 13, folders 1-5. Box 12 contains evidence of a more general reach in the public policy arena as well. His application for Common Cause membership appears in folder 1, his membership on the Federal Power Commission Advisory Committee, folder 6. Box 13 offers more in this vein, i.e., he consults for the National Science Board, National Science Foundation, folder 6, serves as a public member of New York State's Energy Research and Development Authority (NYSERDA), folder 9, and as a member of the Energy Advisory Committee of the Congressional Office of Technology Assessment, folder 10, and sometimes sets priorities as when he resigns from the Natural Resources Defense Council to accept appointment to New York's Emergency Financial Control Board, folder 7, while Box 14, folder 1 identifies his consultancy to the Administrator of the U.S. Energy Research and Development Administration. Frequently he wore his several hats at once, as exemplified in Box 11, folder 13, where, as a Committee for Economic Development (CED) member and a University president, he participates in a CED survey of academic leaders on federal support of research and development, Robert Holland to Thomas Vanderslice 12/28/78, and in Box 14, folder 10, when as Crane Company corporate director and University president he comments on NYU investment strategy 5/23/78.
  Subseries III, found in part of Box 14 and part of Box 15, documents directorship appointment, among them several in the natural resource sector, United Siscoe Mines Ltd., Box 15, folder 6, Geothermal Kinetics, inc., Box 14, folder 12, North American Coal Corporation, Box 15, folder 2, and Consolidated Edison (NY), Box 14, folder 9.
  Subseries IV has been constructed somewhat arbitrarily, to incorporate a miscellany of documents. Among the higher education-related materials in Box 15, see Sawhill to Gail Parker 12/8/75, folder 8. For an NYU response to a CHANGE Magazine survey identifying those institutions NYU saw as peers, to consult with or use as models, 4/15/76, folder 9. Another kind of NYU profile is located in folder 12, a survey of cost-related data and analysis in institutions of higher education. Also among the miscellany were references to the Washington Square Music Festival and the Friends of Washington Square Park, which were transferred to Archives H.
  - Subseries I: NYU-Related, NYC, etc.
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), May 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), Jul 1975-Mar 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Association for a Better New York (ABNY), Sep 1975-Mar 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Association of American Colleges (AAC), Jul 1975-Jan 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York (ACUSNY), Apr 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Business Marketing Corportation, Aug 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Business/Labor Working Group, May 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Business/Labor Working Group, Jul 1976-Nov 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Business/Labor Working Group, Mar 1977-Nov 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Business/Labor Working Group, Mar 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Caring Community, The, Nov 1978-Jan 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Century Association, May 1975-Apr 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Citizens Committee for New York City, Inc., Sep 1975-Jan 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - City Club, The, Feb 1976-Mar 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Coalition for New York; (Metropolitan Council), Feb 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Coalition of Independent College and University Students (COPUS), Jun 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Committee for Astor Place, Mar 1979-Jan 1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Apr 1976-Aug 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Sep 1978-Oct 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Financial Control Board, Jun 1977-Jun 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Financial Control Board, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Financial Control Board, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Emergency Financial Control Board, Jun 1979-Jan 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, Mar 1979-Oct 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Fifth Avenue Association, Mar 1979-Apr 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council, Jan 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Greater NY Conference on Soviet Jewry; (also NY Commission for Prisoners of Conscience), Jul 1978-Aug 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Greenwich Village Chamber of Commerce, Feb 1978-Jun 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Hebrew Union College, Oct 1975-Nov 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX), Dec 1970-Jan 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Lehrman Institute, The, Jun 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mayor's Long Range Planning Committee, May 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Middle States Association, Commission on Higher Education, Aug 1975-Feb 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Municipal Broadcasting System (WNYC), May 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (NAICU), Mar 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), Dec 1979-Apr 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - New York Convention and Visitors Bureau, Jun 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges and Universities, Inc., Jun 1975-Nov 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - New York University Club, Jul 1975-Feb 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - New York University Finance Club; Advisory Council, Sep 1975-Nov 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Parks Safety Committee (NYC Parks Council), Feb 1977-Jun 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture; Sponsors Committee, Aug 1975-Sep 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sun Valley Center for the Arts and Humanities, Mar 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - United Nations University, Sep 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Universities Space Research Association, Sep 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), Jul 1976-Nov 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - World Institute for Computer Assisted Teaching (WICAT), Sep 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Subseries II: Not-for-Profit, energy, etc.
    - Advertising Council, Jun 1976-Sep 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Alliance to Save Energy, Mar 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - American Association for the Advancement of the Humanities, Jul 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - American Council on Germany, Jun 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - American Ditchley Foundation, Mar 1977-Oct 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Americans for Alaska, Mar 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Aspen Institute, Aug 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Aspen Institute, Jan 1978-Feb 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Aspen Institute, Mar 1978-Apr 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Aspen Institute, May 1978-Jun 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Aspen Institute, Jul 1978-Aug 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Aspen Institute, Sep 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Aspen Institute, Nov 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Aspen Institute, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Aspen Institute, Jun 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States, Mar 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie-Mellon Institute of Research, Feb 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Center for Governmental Resposibility, University of Florida, Feb 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Center for Metropolitan Planning and Research; School of Advanced International Studies; Johns Hopkins University, Dec 1974-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Center for Philosophy and Public Policy, Unversity of Maryland, Oct 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - China Institute in America, Inc., Sep 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Coalition for Northeast Governors (CONEG), Nov 1976-Aug 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Economic Development (CED), Feb 1976-Mar 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Committee for Economic Development (CED); Design Committee, Nov 1977-Aug 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Committee for Economic Development (CED); Technology Policy Subcommittee, May 1978-Nov 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Common Cause, Dec 1976-Sep 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), Mar 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), Jan 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), Mar 1978-Oct 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI), Mar 1979-Oct 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Federal Power Commission, National Gas Survey; Supply Technical Advisory Committee, Jul 1975-Jan 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - German Marshall Fund, Oct 1977-Apr 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Helsinki Watch Committee, Oct 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Energy Studies (Stanford University), Mar 1977-Nov 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Socio-economic Studies, Jan 1977-Dec 1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - International Association of Energy Economists, Jul 1978-Apr 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange, Inc., Nov 1975-Jun 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Japan Society, Inc., Aug 1975-Aug 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Japan Society, Inc.; Japan Today Committee, Aug 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Japan Society, Inc.; Shimoda Conference, May 1977-Aug 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Japan Society, Inc.; Shimoda Conference, Sep 1977-Mar 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Japan Society, Inc.; Shimoda Conference; Sawhill Paper and Commentary, Sawhill session III notes, Sep 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Mitre Corporation, Nuclear Energy Policy Study, Apr 1975-Jan 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mitre Corporation, Nuclear Energy Policy Study, Feb 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Mitre Corporation, Nuclear Energy Policy Study, Dec 1976-Jul 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Mitre Corporation, Nuclear Energy Policy Study; Sawhill Chapter Draft, May 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Mitre Corporation, Nuclear Energy Policy Study; Sawhill Chapter Re-draft, Jul 1976-Nov 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - National Science Foundation, National Science Board, Consulting, Sep 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources Defence Council, May 1976-Dec 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - New Directions, Mar 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - New York State Energy Research and Development Authority (NYSERDA), Mar 1976-Nov 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), Jun 1975-Mar 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Resolve, Jul 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Resources for the Future (RFF); Ford (Foundation) Study Group; Energy, the Next 20 Years, Jul 1977-Nov 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Resources for the Future (RFF); Ford (Foundation) Study Group; Energy, the Next 20 Years, Dec 1978-Jan 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Resources for the Future (RFF); Ford (Foundation) Study Group; Energy, the Next 20 Years, Feb 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Association for Club of Rome, Feb 1976-Jun 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Association for Club of Rome, Jul 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), Oct 1976-Nov 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Urban Institute, Jan 1978-Dec 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Whitehead Medical Research Institute, Mar 1977-Sep 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - World Peace Foundation, May 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III: Directorships
    - Accuity Systems, Inc., Nov 1974-Jul 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Jul 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - American International Group (AIG), Sep 1976-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Automatic Data Processing, Inc. (ADP), Jan 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Edison (NY), May 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Crane Company, Jan 1978-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - General American Investors, Feb 1977-Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Geothermal Kinetics, Inc., Apr 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - ICI Americas, Inc., Mar 1978-Oct 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - North American Coal Corporation, Aug 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Philip Morris Incorporated, Apr 1978-Oct 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Radio Corporation of America, Jun 1978-Jan 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Schroder Bank & Trust Company, J. Henry, Oct 1978-Mar 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - United Siscoe Mines Ltd., Oct 1975-Dec 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Subseries IV: Higher Education, Corporate, Personal, etc.
    - Miscellaneous; A, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous; B, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous; C, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous; D-H, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous; I, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous; J-M, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous; N-O, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous; P-Z, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series III: Development
  This series offers a comprehensive picture of John Crittenden Sawhill's fundraising efforts for NYU. It occupies 8 Hollinger boxes, measuring 3.333 linear feet. Correspondence forms the bulk of the series, from which a variety of information can be gleaned. Corporate leaders with little or no prior NYU connection were approached, see Mark Kaplan to Sawhill, 3/7/77, Box 18, folder 6. Sawhill's multiple hat persona appears, see Rawleigh Warner Jr. to Sawhill 1/14/77 and Sawhill to Warner 1/19/77, Box 20, folder 15, as do his views on corporate philanthropy, Sawhill to John S. Burr 4/5/77 in response to Burr to Sawhill 3/23/77, Box 21, folder 11, and a comprehensive snub, General Motors, Box 18, folder 17.
  Some commentary on the Mueller Spaghetti Company sale appears, see Sawhill to Harold K. Hochschild 10/12/76, Box 19, folder 3 and to Alvin C. Zises, 10/15/76, Box 23, folder 3. A picture of extensive exchanges with the Shah of Iran and his representatives in Tehran and the United States emerges, Box 19, folder 5. The impact of the Leadership Campaign on NYU is described 5/9/80 by Ivan Loveridge Bennett Jr. to John E. Marshall III of the Kresge Foundation, Box 19, folder 16. A 7/26/54 analysis of institutional science facilities needs is found in Ray Harvey to David D. Henry, in Olin Foundation, Box 21, folder 8. A "Local Review Statement," on University goals was submitted to the National Science Foundation, 3/15/76, Box 21, folder 2.
  Some connections have substantial history, such as the Gottesman Foundation, from 11/65, Box 18, folder 19, International Business Machines, 10/68, Box 19, folder 6, Mrs. Mary Lasker, 1/55, Box 20, folder 3. Two serendipidously consecutive folders offer a marked contrast between a devoted Washington Square alumnus, Michael Schimmel, and a disaffected University Heights alumnus, Henry R. Schnitzer Foundation, Box 22, folders 1-2. Finally, in Box 23, folder 12, Sawhill speaks to Gallatin Associates as NYU "booster," 12/2/75 and 10/7/76, and in folder 18 the University is profiled in the development 4/77 draft, "Our Presence in New York."
  - Alumni Affairs; Association Lists, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Affairs; Association Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Affairs; Correspondence; (A-D), Aug 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Affairs; Correspondence; (E-L), Aug 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Affairs; Correspondence; (M-P), Aug 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Affairs; Correspondence; (R-W), Aug 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Federation, Jul 1975-Nov 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Federation; Dinner, Oct 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation; Dinner, Jun 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Federation; Dinner, May 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Federation; Dinner, May 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Fund, Alumni Lawyers Reception, Mar 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Luncheons, Jan 1976-Feb 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Corporate Luncheons, Jan 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Corporate Luncheons, Jan 1978-Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Development, General, May 1975-Apr 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising, Campaign, May 1976-Nov 1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising, Campaign; Progress Reports, Oct 1975-Feb 1979 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Aa-Al), Jul 1975-Aug 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (American A-American C), Nov 1976-Jun 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (American D-American T), Apr 1976-Nov 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Am-Ar), Jun 1976-Jan 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (As-Az), Oct 1976-Dec 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ba-Bas), Oct 1976-Nov 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Be-Bh), May 1976-Oct 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Bi- Bn), Oct 1975-Mar 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Bo), Sep 1976-Jan 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Br-Bz), Jan 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ca-Cd), Oct 1976-Nov 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ce-Ch), Dec 1976-Nov 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Chase Manhattan Bank, N.A.), Nov 1975-Sep 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Citibank, formerly First National City Bank), Dec 1974-Jul 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ci-Cl), Aug 1973-Apr 1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Citizens Utilities Company), May 1976-Sep 1980 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Co-Col), Nov 1968-Nov 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Com), Jan 1977-Aug 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Con-Cu), Feb 1976-Oct 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Da-Dd), Sep 1976-Oct 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (De-Di), Nov 1976-Oct 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Do-Dz), Feb 1974-Apr 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ea-Eh), Jun 1976-Feb 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (El-Er), Jan 1973-Jul 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Es-Ez), Sep 1976-Jul 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Exxon Corporation/Education Foundation), Aug 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Fa-Fe), Mar 1973-Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Fi-Fo), Dec 1975-Nov 1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ford Foundation), Apr 1976-Aug 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Fr-Fu), Feb 1971-Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ga-Ge), Sep 1974-Jun 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (General Electric Company/Foundation), Feb 1975-Nov 1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (General Motors Corporation), Jul 1975-Mar 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Gi-Go), Mar 1976-Jan 1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Gottesman Foundation), Nov 1965-Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Gr-Gu), Apr 1963-Jul 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ha), Jun 1976-Aug 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (He), Oct 1972-Jun 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Hi-Hy), Apr 1974-Apr 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Ia-In), Oct 1975-Jul 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Correspondence; (Iran), Mar 1968-Nov 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)